AYU NAMIRA QUALITY ASSURANCE

Jakarta, Indonesia | HP: 082261081855 | Email: ayunami12@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ayu-namira-217a3b277

SUMMARY

Graduate of Politeknik Negeri Lhokseumawe. I am interested in the quality assurance manual and automation. I have one year of experience working as a manual quality assurance. I have basic skill critical thinking and need a lot to learn more. I enjoyed working with the team. I hope to gain my knowledge and experience can contribute to the company.

EXPERIENCE

CAREER DEVELOPMENT CENTER POLITEKNIK NEGERI LHOKSEUMAWE (Freelance) - Aceh Admin (July 2021 – August 2021)

- Communication with student alumni to check data on alumni 2019.
- Data entry student alumni 2019 to website.

PT PERTA ARUN GAS (Contract) – Aceh, Indonesia

Quality Assurance Manual Tester (February 2020 – January 2021)

- Analysis and design database of application master equipment.
- Analysis and design database of application daily operation report.
- Design user interface of web master equipment.
- Design user interface of web daily operation report.
- Design user experience of web master equipment.
- Design user experience of web daily operation report.
- Testing manual of application master equipment.
- Testing manual of application daily operation report.
- Create bug report of application master equipment.
- Create bug report of application daily operation report.
- Create user guidelines for application master equipment.
- Create user guidelines for application daily operation report.
- Socialization of software user procedures.
- Data entry of application master equipment.
- Data entry of application daily operation report.

PROJECT

- Application Master Equipment.
- Application Daily Operation Report.

(Freelance) - Aceh, Indonesia

Quality Assurance Manual Tester (August 2019 - September 2019)

- Tracking bug.
- Create bug report using Microsoft Word.
- Testing of User Acceptance Testing (UAT).
- Create user guidelines for STK Online 3.0.

PROJECT

Application STK Online 3.0.

PT PLN (Persero) Rayon Lhokseumawe Kota (Internship) - Aceh, Indonesia

Pelayanan Teknik (YANTEK) (July 2018 – August 2018)

- Serving customer complaints.
- Data entry customer complaints into the Aplikasi Keluhan dan Pengaduan Terpadu (APKT).
- Recording the load and voltage of the substation.
- Fieldwork with the technical service team to conduct ground resistance measurements (grounding).
- Fieldwork with the technical service team to check for damage and repair of NT Fuse transformers.
- Fieldwork with the technical service team to check the meters on house connection cables.

EDUCATION

POLITEKNIK NEGERI LHOKSEUMAWE - Formal (2015 - 2019)

D4 of Computer Information Technology - GPA 3.44/3.5

MAN 1 Lhokseumawe - Formal (2011 - 2014)

Science

BINAR ACADEMY - Non Formal (June 2023 - October 2023)

Quality Assurance Engineer

SKILLS

- Tools: TestRail, Cucumber, Postman API, Jmeter, Jira, Trello, Katalon, Appium, GitLab, GitHub.
- Hard Skill: Test Cases, Test Scenarios, Bug Tracking, Bug Report, Manual Testing, Gherkin, Data Entry, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel.
- Soft Skill: Critical Thinking, Working with the Team, Time Management, Responsible.

LANGUAGE

- Indonesia.
- English (Beginner).

PORTFOLIO

https://namiayu1.github.io/ayunamira.github.io/